# Andries Mpontseng Sebola

#### Software developer.

I am a very dedicated and passionate towards learning and improving my programming skills provide reliable solutions to the technological industry and the community at large.

3 years' experience as a Software developer through hands-on experience

#### Contact

**Contact:** +27 637838676

Email: andriesmpontsheng@gmail.com

Linkedin: (33) Andries Sebola | LinkedIn

Github: andries-ui (Andries Mpontseng

sebola) (github.com)

<u>Portfolio:</u> https://andriesui.github.io/portfolio/

## Language

- English
- Sepedi

## **Highlights**

## Interpersonal skills

- ♦ Transparency
- ♦ Positive attitude
- Solution focus
- ♦ Flexible
- ♦ Strong communication
- ♦ Active listener
- ♦ Works well in Team work and individually
- ♦ Confident speaking

#### • Front-end and Backend

- ♦ React native
- ♦ React.js
- ♦ JavaScript
- ♦ TypeScript
- ♦ Java
- ◆ C#
- ♦ C++
- ♦ Xamarin forms
- ♦ Xamarin Android
- ♦ SQL
- ♦ CSS
- ♦ PL/SQL
- ♦ HTML5

## Other application

- ♦ Jira, Bit bucket, Trello, Xamarin Android
- PHP Storm, Visual studio code, Git,
   Photoshop, Figma ,studio

# Software applications and Operating Systems

- Microsoft technologies including visual studio 2010 − 17, Xcode and Android studio
- ◆ Expo CLi, React CLi, .NET, Cordova Cli
- ♦ Linux server
- Rest API, MySQL, NoSQL, PL/SQL, Firebase, MongoDB, Express js

## **Experience**

06/2021-03/2022

MLAB Limpopo: Coding Programme (10 months)

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, React Js, React Native

Other tools: Firebase, MongoDB, SQLite, figma.

08/2021-12/2021

Novo Digital: Junior developer (4 months)

Languages: JavaScript, React Native Other tools: express js, mySql, Figma.

## **Education**

2017-2021

National Diploma in Software development: Tshwane university of technology

06/2021-03/2022

CodeTribe: HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Firebase, React js , React native

**AgriTour Hackerthon:** Limpopo Agritour certificate of attendance.

#### References

## MLAB Limpopo CodeTribe facilitator

facilitator: Tyson Motlhabeng

contact: +27 78 649 8402 email: tyson@mlab.co.za

Novo digital director
Director: Karabo ngoatla

contact: +27 83 696 4625 email: karabo@novodigital.biz